epharmapedia.com 2016-10-15

# Privacy policy | ePharmapedia

At ePharmaPedia, we value your privacy and we know that no one has the right to know your personal information without your permission.

The privacy of our members is our priority, which means the information you share with us is protected. Here, you need to know that there is a difference between the personal information found in your registration form, and the information that you submit to be put in our directories; more information about this can be found below.

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or submit information to be added to our directories. 

When you do any of these, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and/or credit card information.

**What do we use your information for?  **  
The information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve customer service   
(your information helps us to respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you decide to join our mailing list, you will receive emails that include ePharmaPedia news, updates, related products or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to discontinue receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your information. 

All the transaction and payment operations on our website are done through third parties that offer the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and are then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers' database to be accessible only to those who are authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?  **  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow them) that enable the sites or service providers' systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information to make your browsing easier. 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits, such as your preferred language.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. Generally, however, you can still benefit from our services.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  **  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links  **  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  **  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years or older.

**Profile Data**  
No one will see the information contained in your registration form. However, the contact information in your profile that you submit to be added to our directories will appear to the members of our website. You should know that there's a difference between your registration information and your profile information, meaning that you can put different information in your profile and your registration form. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only  **  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions  **  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [Terms of Use](http://www.epharmapedia.com/page/termsofuse?lang=en).

**Your Consent  **  
By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy  **  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and it will be sent to your email.
